filecyb.org 2008-06-15

# File Cyb.org - Your #1 provider of shared files and fast downloads!

## FileCyb.org Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Welcome to FileCyb.org. We want you to know that we respect your privacy and that we value your business. This privacy statement covers the Raptor software, FileCyb.org software and the FileCyb.org website (www.filecyb.org). In order to ensure your privacy we want you to know the details of what information we collect and what we do with it. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

FileCyb.org takes your privacy very seriously. In order to provide you with the highest quality service, we do collect certain information from you in accordance with the following guidelines. 

#### Direct Submissions:

In order to provide you with excellent service and a superior customer experience FileCyb.org has several areas where you can submit information to us and we also have features that automatically collect information from users of our service. Some of the information you may choose to provide includes personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email, age, gender and interests. In addition, we may collect information linked to your communications preferences, and your payment and billing information. 

#### Cookies and Other Technology:

FileCyb.org may use cookies or other technologies for several purposes all designed to improve the customer experience. Within the FileCyb.org service we may use either what are commonly called temporary or "session" cookies as well as permanent or "persistent" cookies. Temporary or "session" cookies mean that they only last as long as you are online. We may use these cookies to identify you as a valid member so that we can deliver files to you, and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre choice, your connection speed, etc). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we may provide. These cookies do not contain any personally identifying information and we do not store data collected by them.

We may sometimes use cookies, as well as other tracking technology, such as web beacons, within the promotional emails that we send to our members or advertisements for our service or sites. These technologies help us track, for example, whether an e-mail recipient has completed an event, such as signing up for a trial. The generated information is related to non-personally identifiable customer identification numbers and is only analyzed at aggregate levels. We may send these emails via third-party service providers that act on our behalf.

We sometimes utilize third party service providers to help us track the activity and user flows within our service or sites. These third parties may use temporary cookies and/or web beaconing technology to facilitate such tracking. Such tracking would track an individual user's movements but the data would not be tracked in a personally identifiable way. Such data would be stored and analyzed on an aggregated basis for purposes of internal analysis by FileCyb.org to continue to optimize our customer experience.

If we engage with any advertising partners and or other third parties, our approved advertising partners and third parties whose products or services are promoted on our site may also use cookies, and we advise you to check their privacy policies for information about their cookies and other privacy practices if you are presented with one of their offers during your association with FileCyb.org.

#### Cookies and Other Technology:

FileCyb.org may use cookies or other technologies for several purposes all designed to improve the customer experience. Within the FileCyb.org service we may use either what are commonly called temporary or "session" cookies as well as permanent or "persistent" cookies. Temporary or "session" cookies mean that they only last as long as you are online. We may use these cookies to identify you as a valid member so that we can deliver files to you, and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre choice, your connection speed, etc). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we may provide. These cookies do not contain any personally identifying information and we do not store data collected by them.

#### Log Files and ip addresses:

We use internet protocol (ip) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. ip addresses are not linked by FileCyb.org to personally identifiable information and are not kept after the statistics are logged in the aggregated database. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. It is not shared with other organizations. However, users should be aware that both static and dynamic ip addresses can be mapped back to users on most ISPs based on the users login time and recorded information.

### LINKS

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link from or frame within the FileCyb.org website. We may also participate in co-branding, advertising and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our users. Information about you may be visible to subsequent websites if you link off of the FileCyb.org website. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners, advertisers or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) is not received by us. As such, we are not responsible for, or have any control over, the content or the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read theprivacy policies of each and every website visited when linking from FileCyb.org.com. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by FileCyb.org.

### CHOICE/OPT-OUT

As a member of FileCyb.org, you can download, search, share and publish just about any digital file. Users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of the sharing component of the FileCyb.org Software, so that such user's files are not made available to other users, by disabling that component of the Software. Each user is provided with the option to disable the sharing component of the Software by going into the preferences section of our site and "disabling" the appropriate component...

Additionally you can modify your registration and preferences information at any time in the My Account section of our service. Also all of FileCyb.org's promotional emails are accompanied with information on how to change your communications preferences and how to "opt-out" of certain communications. For access to our communications preferences page please go to the My Account section of the Service.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the FileCyb.org website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

At times FileCyb.org may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance that disclosure of information is necessary.

### SECURITY

We take every reasonable precaution to protect information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although we cannot guarantee that users' information will not be subject to unauthorized access, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we may collect online. All employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify registered users by way of an e-mail or instant messaging or similar method, and/or by posting a notice on our website.

### QUESTIONS

If you have questions or concerns regarding this please email us at [privacy@filecyb.org](mailto:privacy@filecyb.org).
